=The Little Red Matchmaker= =Episode 3=
=صانع الثقاب الأحمر الصغير= =الحلقة 3=
Master.
يتقن.
Master, are you alright?
أستاذ هل أنت بخير؟
I was worried about you.
كنت قلقا عليك.
I'll get out of here.
سأخرج من هنا.
Wait a moment.
انتظر لحظة.
Master.
يتقن.
The shape of your rash looks strange.
شكل الطفح الجلدي الخاص بك يبدو غريبا.
(No.)
(لا.)
(I can't let her know my secret.)
(لا أستطيع أن أخبرها بسرّي).
(How come the rash on my hands)
(كيف يأتي الطفح الجلدي على يدي)
(disappeared so quickly this time?)
(اختفى بهذه السرعة هذه المرة؟)
Master,
يتقن،
this medicine is so good.
هذا الدواء جيد جدا.
It works instantly.
إنه يعمل على الفور.
(Who exactly is she?)
(من هي بالضبط؟)
(That definitely wasn't the effect of the ointment.)
(وهذا بالتأكيد لم يكن تأثير المرهم).
(Well,)
(حسنًا،)
(could touching her cure my illness?)
(هل لمسها يعالج مرضي؟)
I've heard that Miss Zhang is unwed.
لقد سمعت أن الآنسة تشانغ غير متزوجة.
She excels at music, chess, calligraphy, and painting.
إنها تتفوق في الموسيقى والشطرنج والخط والرسم.
She truly is
انها حقا
a graceful and virtuous lady.
سيدة رشيقة وفاضلة.
I can read it upside down.
أستطيع قراءتها رأسا على عقب.
Have you finished your study?
هل انتهيت من دراستك؟
Zhao, Qian, Sun, Li,
تشاو، تشيان، صن، لي،
Zhou, Wu, Zheng, Wang.
تشو، وو، تشنغ، وانغ.
Tall, handsome, and short ones.
طويل القامة، وسيم، وقصير.
None of them is good.
لا أحد منهم جيد.
Jiang Changqing, I...
جيانغ تشانغ تشينغ، أنا...
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I...
أنا...
I'm tired.
أنا متعب.
Just stretching a bit.
مجرد تمتد قليلا.
(Mei Siyue)
(مي سييو)
(I missed one.)
(لقد فاتني واحدة.)
(Found you, Mei Siyue.)
(وجدتك، مي سيوي.)
(Zhuque Street)
(شارع زوك)
Master, how long haven't you been out?
سيدي، منذ متى لم تخرج؟
Where are you taking me?
أين تأخذني؟
Master, look at the braised carp.
يا معلم، انظر إلى سمك الشبوط المطهو ​​ببطء.
You're a foodie.
أنت من عشاق الطعام.
It's so lively tonight.
انها حية جدا هذه الليلة.
Sugar-coated haws.
الزعرور المغلفة بالسكر.
Master.
يتقن.
I take one.
أنا آخذ واحدة.
Here.
هنا.
It's delicious.
إنه لذيذ.
Thank you, Master.
شكرا لك أيها السيد.
Master, you eat first.
يا معلم، تأكل أولا.
Eating too many sweets can harm your health.
تناول الكثير من الحلويات يمكن أن يضر بصحتك.
You're a good doctor.
أنت طبيب جيد.
You can cure me.
يمكنك علاجي.
That's why I'm not afraid.
لهذا السبب أنا لست خائفا.
Sugar-coated haws.
الزعرور المغلفة بالسكر.
Ever since I got sick,
منذ أن مرضت،
it's been a long time since I've relaxed.
لقد مر وقت طويل منذ أن استرخيت.
Master.
يتقن.
Don't run around.
لا تركض.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
(Oh, no.)
(أوه، لا.)
(The strange illness flared up again.)
(لقد اندلع المرض الغريب مرة أخرى.)
(Where is she?)
(أين هي؟)
♪Years pass by like a dream♪
♪السنوات تمر كالحلم ♪
♪My yearning turns into a melody♪
♪يتحول شوقي إلى لحن♪
♪You are my eternal love in heart♪
♪أنت حبي الأبدي في القلب♪
♪My past life fades like clouds dispersing♪
♪ حياتي الماضية تتلاشى مثل تفرق السحب ♪
♪As I meet you in this life♪
♪ كما التقيت بك في هذه الحياة ♪
♪A thousand years of waiting is not in vain♪
♪ ألف سنة من الانتظار لم تذهب سدى ♪
♪Dreaming in a cool, long night♪
♪ أحلم في ليلة باردة طويلة ♪
♪Who is waiting alone♪
♪ من ينتظر وحده ♪
♪My endless yearning stretches on♪
♪ يمتد شوقي الذي لا نهاية له ♪
♪Despite the hard fate♪
♪ رغم المصير الصعب ♪
♪I hope to reconnect with you♪
♪أتمنى إعادة التواصل معك♪
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
I told you not to run around.
قلت لك ألا تركض.
Master.
يتقن.
Isn't that Dr. Jiang?
أليس هذا الدكتور جيانغ؟
He's hanging out.
إنه يتسكع.
That's Dr. Jiang.
هذا الدكتور جيانغ.
At arm's length?
على مسافة ذراع؟
At palm's length.
على طول الكف.
Look at him.
انظر اليه.
So handsome.
وسيم جدا.
Master.
يتقن.
You're hurting me.
أنت تؤذيني.
Sorry.
آسف.
Master.
يتقن.
You really don't like women.
أنت حقا لا تحب النساء.
Who said that?
من قال هذا؟
A peanut vendor in front of our clinic.
بائع الفول السوداني أمام عيادتنا.
No peanuts allowed.
غير مسموح بالفول السوداني.
♪I asked Yue Lao to give me a relationship♪
♪ طلبت من يو لاو أن يمنحني علاقة ♪
♪But Yue Lao always failed♪
♪ لكن يو لاو يفشل دائمًا ♪
♪I hope to have a fairytale romance♪
♪ أتمنى أن أحظى بقصة رومانسية خيالية ♪
Time to go home.
موعد الذهاب للمنزل.
Not now.
ليس الآن.
(Mei)
(مي)
The mortal world is very dangerous.
العالم البشري خطير جدا.
(To be continued)
(يتبع)
Changqing!
تشانغتشينغ!
♪As the moonlit night is drawing on♪
♪ مع اقتراب الليل المقمر ♪
♪A solitary wild goose is flying in the fog♪
♪ أوزة برية منفردة تطير في الضباب ♪
♪The waning moon is deep in thought♪
♪ القمر المتضائل غارق في التفكير ♪
♪Shedding a golden light over the road♪
♪ إلقاء ضوء ذهبي على الطريق ♪
♪I'm longing for returning home♪
♪ أنا مشتاق للعودة إلى المنزل ♪
♪I abandoned cultivation for a new life♪
♪ لقد تخليت عن الزراعة من أجل حياة جديدة ♪
♪And for the beauty in my heart♪
♪ وللجمال الذي في قلبي ♪
♪We meet only in dreams♪
♪نلتقي فقط في الأحلام♪
♪Souls entwine over the time♪
♪تتشابك الأرواح مع مرور الوقت♪
♪The shattered fate breaks the bond♪
♪ المصير المحطم يكسر الرابطة ♪
♪Years pass by like a dream♪
♪السنوات تمر كالحلم ♪
♪My yearning turns into a melody♪
♪يتحول شوقي إلى لحن♪
♪You are my eternal love in heart♪
♪أنت حبي الأبدي في القلب♪
♪My past life fades like clouds dispersing♪
♪ حياتي الماضية تتلاشى مثل تفرق السحب ♪
♪As I meet you in this life♪
♪ كما التقيت بك في هذه الحياة ♪
♪A thousand years of waiting is not in vain♪
♪ ألف سنة من الانتظار لم تذهب سدى ♪
♪Dreaming in a cool, long night♪
♪ أحلم في ليلة باردة طويلة ♪
♪Who is waiting alone♪
♪ من ينتظر وحده ♪
♪My endless yearning stretches on♪
♪ يمتد شوقي الذي لا نهاية له ♪
♪Despite the hard fate♪
♪ رغم المصير الصعب ♪
♪I hope to reconnect with you♪
♪أتمنى إعادة التواصل معك♪
♪And spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪ وأقضي بقية حياتي معك ♪